Hi everyone! Welcome to another video and it's my first real lingerie dedicated
video. I'm only showing you lingerie from Hunkermüller today. So normally I see a lot
of colorful frilly designs from Hunkermüller but I found these two. A 4 letter set
and a PVC lingerie set. So I thought I'm going to try them. So yeah let's do it!
I love how this looks. It seems like they combined a bra and the harness here because it's a nice harness part. So I think under a t-shirt with a wider cleavage and when you can see this, it's going to look really cool.
or under some see-through tops. So yeah, it is really comfortable, I have to say that,
because it's not always the case. But I quite like it. I mean, it's a bit, yeah, a bit
less fabric than I'm used to, especially here. But with all the three stripes here, I feel a bit
dressed at least because it covers a wider part here in this area. I don't know.
So it almost feels like a whole outfit because of this extraordinary design
and this yeah special material. I don't know, a four-letter bra is not what you usually find
at the stores I guess. It is a slightly push-up effect so it's a padded bra and
the details are golden. I do have to keep looking for more golden accessories to
match them and the straps are not size adjustable but they fit me anyway which
is quite cool. Oh by the way I bought my usual size and it fits so it's true to
size which is always a good sign and I think I'm going to switch to the next
one now. Second set the PVC set and it is shiny and I'm wearing the high waist
panty I think there was also a low cut string or like a less fabric option for
the panty here but I decided on this one and I quite like the back view here
and that the design matches here and like here really looks good together
it's almost like a top with the longer cut here in the bra which I like because
I know it is something different and not the usual bra cut and also the strap is
detachable so I can remove it. So if you want to wear this on the t-shirt and
don't want to show this strappy thing you can leave it at home and I think I
don't know it's a look. It's comfortable and I like it. I paired it with some glossy
heels this time to complete the look. So I know that lingerie videos are not my
usual stuff but I wanted to ask you if you'd like to see more of them should I
show more lingerie? any kind of lingerie? leave a comment down below and also tell
me which set you prefer the faux leather one or the PVC one or if you already own
Honka Möller lingerie or your girlfriend so leave a comment down below and I
I think I'm going to show you one last set. My basic go-to lingerie so to say.
So this is basically my go-to daily underwear. It's just a plain black bra and panty.
Although it's really smooth so you do not see it under t-shirts and stuff like that.
It's nearly invisible. And also it is a super push-up bra.
So if you are looking for a comfortable push-up bra I can recommend this basic one here.
Also for the panty it has laser cut edges so there are no thick seams here and they do work perfectly on the leggings.
So they're like invisible panties and I love to wear them on every kind of pants and leggings.
Alright, I hope you enjoyed this video. I think I have to sneeze. And if you did, leave
a thumbs up or subscribe to my channel. Also, have another look around and watch some other
videos. Have a nice day, bye!